Airmen, soldiers, sailors, and Marines participated in an international basketball
game with other NATO allies.
Airman Benjamin Landon has the story.
When you think about basketball, the first thing that probably
comes to your mind isn't the military.
But for the community on SHAPE, basketball is a big
deal this week as countries within NATO are coming together
for the IBT.
The USA team traveled all the way to Belgium for
their first game in the tournament against Italy.
While the game was slow for the first two quarters,
both teams picked up the pace as they went head
to head on the court, and the competition was getting
tough.
After the buzzer rang in the fourth quarter, Italy walked
away with a win with a two-point lead over
USA.
But this is the first game for the U.S. as
they try to take the title of the International Basketball
Tournament champions.
I'm Airman Benjamin Landon.